alright guys let's see if that's gonna
work is it better I'm holding the phone
in the best possible way oh is it good
is it high-quality now much better okay
excellent sweet sometimes you just gotta
restart the periscope like I was saying
everybody what do you want to do you
wanna Zuckerberg Oh what do you not
wanting to happen you don't want to be
colonic that's right
desire burgum don't get to LACMA okay
cool well so now that that's out of the
way I'm gonna reveal corporate secrets
and I can do this because I am yeah I
got a sucker program that's right
because I'm the majority shareholder and
soul board member of comedy yeah I keep
control of your company kids even though
Steve Jobs did lead a heroic comeback
I'm not sure the same move is in the
cards for mr. clack Nick um so you got a
Zuckerberg um don't get khalaq Nick
alright now that that's over let's talk
okay so we are coming it could be the
Android and self-driving cars so if i
zoom down a little bit here you'll see
that Android runs on LG Samsung HTC One
Plus and many others come a I runs on
Honda Toyota GM and Ford
despite the automakers not wanting to be
a phone manufacturer they are because
the car is the phone and the real reason
people buy the phone is for the Android
not for phone it's kind of interesting
how that works out so I'm sorry car
manufacturers if you don't want to be
Foxconn you will lose if you want to be
Foxconn you got shemail in I'm sure
that's the right strategy for the
automaker really focus on what you're
good at manufacturing um you know you
guys are crushing your crush some tests
that manufacture you know if you guys
saw Elon Musk's letter oh man you guys
this letter dude yo let's go through it
it's actually pretty good you on must is
an absolute boss for writing this letter
some of the things that he says
some part suppliers will be unwilling to
achieve this level of precision I
understand that this would be considered
an unreasonable request by some that's
okay there's lots a lot of car companies
with much lower standards they just
can't work with Tesla see that guy is
great that guy's great because there
isn't a reason to do this
he just likes the idea of things being
good and that's what we need in the
world in order to drive the world
forward you want to say hi to Vasco peas
on Scobie Sunday terrible yeah yeah oh
well we're revealing purpose secrets
we're talking about how you know always
the theme you want to Zuckerberg them
and you don't want to get collabnet but
if you're Elizabeth Holmes and you
commit massive fraud you get off of that
yeah have later on fine so I you know
I'm not reserve judgment on whether you
want a why'd you want to be able to pump
but you certainly don't want B Martin
shkreli you don't want to be Martin
shkreli you gotta be Elizabeth Holmes
you got to be you got to be pretty and
contrite and not you know shkreli
looking and a dick lessons lessons to
learn lessons like thank you say thank
you okay
priests Crowley that's I am all for from
shkreli you guys know that up for free
and shkreli I think that what you did
was you know being a dick is not a crime
this is America we have freedom to be a
dick I love America and I love freedom
yeah fraud yeah if you actually like if
people actually lost money he should
like Pam back maybe a few times over
um but okay cool I don't think that that
really happened I don't know how much
money was lost on her on us but you know
him and the Chang album you know he did
he did you know
ain't nothing to with right and he
the hotel clean so you know
that's what happens all right cool um
any show you the secret project I don't
know what the secret project is um this
is very funny if following your company
rule is obviously ridiculous and it
would make sure Craig Tilburg cartoon
then the rule should change
notice how important he is in the
importance of very clear communication
and I'm a big fan of this to like you
know don't use acronyms or nonsense
words you're objects a lot of things are
actually really simple if you just
explain them in straightforward ways um
one of the you know groups of people in
the world is people who benefit off of
keeping things complex and dad like
turbo tax so don't do that okay excess
means to the plight of big companies
yeah everyone wants to get rid of
meetings get rid of meetings I like this
is not rude to leave it is rude to make
someone stay and waste their time just
just just a great thing about today is
this oh it's frozen okay well I'm sorry
if we tried its back is it good
frozen oh okay is it actually fine okay
it's good all right cool back to Mexico
side cuz if it's not good I'm over this
okay guys what we're gonna try to do is
we have two week Sprint's here where
we're trying to get open pilot release
every sprint we got to move to being a
more serious company yeah yeah so so so
so new models localizer calibration that
will get us all the way down to 0.5 so
we're on we're on 0 for 5 now working
our way down to zero five zero five
we're going to be focused on models and
Maps Honda Toyota GM Ford and the first
0.5 is gonna use maps for red lights and
stop signs and we're also going to have
for the first time driver monitoring so
we're getting back all your front camera
data thank you to people who are helping
out and giving us front camera data wow
talk about 0.6 let's talk about one
thing at a time I don't know if we're
actually gonna do close pilot I think
it's gonna stay open we are on 0 for 4
because guys it's always day one I don't
know who that even that's that's Jeff
Bezos now um how does driver monitoring
work at the dark it that it works how do
you can someone see can you see in the
dark well you can and so can the camera
you just gotta crank the games up it's
day one at Amazon that's true it's not
dead wanna comment I it stays zero point
four point five oh we want to get to day
one it's not even dead one yet did one
you know one point I was gonna be on our
consumer product release that won't kind
of everyone kind of knows at the arc of
calm a guy is actually incredibly
straightforward you know I've been
saying the exact same thing for years
and years now but see the thing is we
are going to ship a self-driving car by
the end of the year for under a thousand
dollars it's up to the end of the year
part hangman but I don't know about that
so zero point five models and maps we're
gonna use zero point five the maps will
be used for red lights and stop signs
we're gonna ship driver monitor and
we're gonna have support for Honda
Toyota GM and Ford new models are
finally happening our head of machine
learning starts again on Monday we got a
new head of machine learning start
something like that and we're gonna make
models and if he doesn't make models I'm
gonna fire and I'm gonna make the models
myself so that's what's gonna happen
we're gonna have models in ten weeks no
matter what whether we have to fire they
had a machine learning or not no the
other one did not last long they don't
do well I will do it I'll do it myself
if it doesn't work so yeah dad over over
yep they're gone gone so that's why
there's new models
yeah a lot of God you can fix the fan
yeah no people get fired a lot around
here like do work and do well and be
smart or you're fired
um but you know it makes it makes
quality and it makes us like it makes us
an office opposed to work because you
may just drive by smart people no
pressure new guy well you know a lot of
pressure the new guy no no I'm no fresh
new guy just do well okay cool um so we
are also hiring for three positions um
here's our current layout of the company
we're hiring for two people on the
mapping team and one person on the
monitoring team not Linux admins we're
looking for a full stack developer
looking for somebody knows about sensors
and hardware and we're looking for
somebody knows that ml and data science
to monitor all the users you know what
we're monitoring the driver right so
we're gonna write some some sick some
sick face rack and he's actually kind of
got someone joining him you know we're
gonna try to sales have been sales seven
skyrocketing so we're gonna try to do
filament maybe even more often I know we
do a lot of training in the basement um
no civil engineering jobs
definitely not there's only two
legitimate roles at a company on the to
legitimate roles at a company are
engineering and that's what these first
five are and operations that's what the
bottom line here is so engineering build
things and operation ships things and
ensures they continue running I'm not
really sure we need QA it seems our be
false and just got a big team and he's
got a four-person team now but you know
any killer we're very happy with Andy a
fusion going pretty well
Ricardo's been working on it this week
um but no who are we hiring for we're
hiring a full stack engineer for the
mapping team basically we have the maps
we just need somebody who can build the
UI build like a nice UI for us to
explore ante
and improve the maps you don't look for
bugs and stuff so looking for a full
stack developer to do that you know
stick the maps of the database yeah we
have two interns coming this summer if
you're interested in an internship give
me a job at comedy I and you can be an
intern so we're looking for someone here
who's gonna do sensors and hardware and
timing timing is very important you know
you want to make accurate maps it's very
important to get your timing right and
then we're looking for somebody to own
the driver monitoring project so I wrote
the code that records the front camera
we're looking for somebody who's gonna
work on interpreting that code so we're
hire there are no no opportunities and
operations you see the question marks
the question marks are the places where
there are opportunities no it's not
infrastructure monitoring if the
structure falls under product its driver
modern so we need ml and data science Oh
compensation is quite good okay well and
I don't know if you believe in our
equity but oh yeah this girl was texting
me back how exciting well that's great I
know we don't have a remote employees
what about that prototyping or cancel to
cancel absolutely cancels so over that
prototype beyond yawns have been used
but if you guys know so we're gonna go
to China we're gonna look for more one
plus three T's because you guys have
been buying yawns at an astronomical
rate which is great we love sales but
you know it just means we got to make
more so yeah guys we're hiring for these
three positions if you know anyone Oh
any improvements on ping pong well
ping-pong is gonna be fixed when we have
this and when we have these we need to
localize it may need calibration and we
need the new models but 0.5 should not
paint how much call your friends is
telling you I don't want a sony phone
today honestly standing there yawn back
we don't sell Goosby on zorg only sell
new yachts so yeah we're trying to do a
release every sprint so that's every two
weeks you're welcome for horizontal
video I understand you guys like it Tork
approve it's a Honda never never you
worry never know happening when I
releasing epsp flashes at least for a
long time because the dangerous let me
tell you what can happen if you reflash
the EPS alright let me tell you why
they're dangerous if you do it wrong you
do it right it's not dangerous but you
do it wrong stages okay so if a torque
sensor in here and you have any PS here
and you have a motor here all right I'm
sorry this is connected here this
connected here this is connected to the
steering column here the wheels your car
and your the wheels and here's the
steering column through the motor and
here's the week right here's the problem
this motor is stronger than you and the
only thing we can get to by the pedals
much less dangerous in a second the
motor here is stronger than you um if
you flash the wrong software here you
will make you can make the wheel turn
and the user literally not be able to
override it
um so EPS three flashes can be quite
dangerous why is the pedal much less
dangerous who knows who knows why the
pedal is much less dangerous than you
asking for just a few petals up here
I'll go we also have an EPS is the toy
80 PS yeah you can just hit the brake um
you can hit the brake you can put the
car in neutral you have a lot of options
in the absolute worst case if you get
unintended acceleration right um yeah
the brake is stronger than the gas and
there's a way to override it right also
the other thing too is if this thing
even jerks the wheel you're in trouble
um yeah cars have live mode they're
quite good if it jerks the gas that's
you're fine all right you'll hear the
engine rev opulent
the brakes maybe maybe a pedal would be
much more dangerous on the Tesla but a
pedal on a rav4 you can floor the rav4
and it's not going anywhere yeah
assuming the disengage still works but
if you put the wrong code on the EPS you
could be in trouble
so what's not dangerous if you do it
right the problem is who's doing it
right right um so no epsp flashes stop
complaining about the park you know what
you know what you know what Eric moraga
would say if you want more torque it's
al fondo by Toyota GM seems to have more
torque as well I don't know about the
words torque but by Toyota um so no I
can see flashes okay notice how that's
not on board for anyway but I mean look
like if so many figures it out I hope
they will have the sensibility to not
release it be so anti yet there are ways
to do it safe um vault progress we're
thinking about buying one we thinking
about buying a Chevy ah Sal Honda by
Toyota
what we do with the red lights or stop
signs well we'll do exactly what you
think we will stop at red lights we can
actually also automatically go at red
lights as well um so we can stop any go
at red lights stop signs we're gonna
stop and then we're gonna ask the user
to press the button and then you can go
when the user decide that it's safe
because we don't have enough cameras to
see we don't have enough cameras on the
common Eon to see red lights and stop
signs they're coming out in 0.5 cool
bros I think that's mostly Skokie Sunday
yeah that'll be in zero five um I tried
ml the student data on the previous I
don't know Lane changing the lane
changing it's not that useful I don't
know I tried on the Tesla I was I was
pretty uh underwhelmed a 0.5 will be out
before the end of the year yeah when
does the Sprint timer start well so
we're gonna do a release
0 for 5 in a week 0 for 6 two weeks
after that and you can predict when 0
for 5 s 0 fast enough 0 5 will be out
before the NBA gets exciting stuff so
we're given we have a seven week machine
learning plan to get you guys new models
and then if this doesn't work out you
know we fire one more head of machine
learning and I do it myself
periscope is plug
I kind of agree yeah well commas next
product be level three next product whoa
how many of you fires six people some
people well not exactly
you run exactly five it's a long story
it's a launch third we're not gonna not
go discuss the details of employees here
HR might yellow gotta watch out you
always got to make HR happy that's your
job any company tell no facebook HR
operations
alright scobie's it's being look at me
stream on YouTube I don't know man I
honestly like Twitter's platform better
than Google
I'm sorry periscope sucks we should make
our own periscope um have you had open
file stay again just stop sending torque
to wheel and not really it shouldn't
happen any new debug tools no no no you
know all the debug tools we can go look
you want to go your quality's amazing
excellent love it you wanna go look at
the at this stuff oh yo ho y'all wanna
hear some crazy guys you see these
these are the last 228 gig eons in
existence
that's it when these two get bought
no more 128kb yawns so the main thing
that we're talking about on this copy
Sunday how long are the internships
twelve weeks main thing that we're
talking about Muscovy sunday is the DSP
yeah probably
probably maybe the next one yeah I've
been working on DSP code guys know has
been that's been my little project
when is China trip soon soon soon soon
yo-yo yes seriously
you know it was might be a good
investment oh if we run out I don't know
really what's gonna happen maybe we
should raise prices you know a comma we
always try to read prices of our
hardware remember that time pandas were
$88 I can't find an 88 dollar panda now
hoodies man buyer shit's good investment
all right scope ease thank you for
joining I don't know where is head talk
Michael public yo check out free the DSP
calm that's free in the DSP for all the
people to use I don't know why I give
this away for free we should keep
it all secret and then charge people a
lot of money but not we give it away for
free because the pie will be big and
every will be happy you got a panda for
50 no way not for me again bra overview
of how I freed the DSP I don't know read
the code man you're on to moon haughtily
on coin yo seriously
yawns our limited-edition yawns are also
you know come a I look
we're phone manufacturer right yeah that
$88 pan at we're for manufacture and if
you guys have seen the trend uh with
phones oh we got plenty of men i blacks
but 128 gigs are low so there's that no
but um if you've seen the trend with
phones phones are expensive these days
and I think we're gonna get on that
trend whoo so you know get your Rhian no
naughty on - there's no we on - I
promise you there's no e on - there's
not even gonna be in yon there was we
were thinking about a neon with a
different phone but they're definitely
not be any on to why no active marketing
because marketing is stupid right um we
have X budget as a company right and we
spent it all on engineers and operations
anything you spend on marketing is a
sunk cost we don't need to market we
just need to make a product better if we
can make our product so good won't you
marketing there just won't be anything
like it
imagine only one company made
refrigerators would you need to market
them food want to keep it cold buy a
refrigerator no does everyone have a
refrigerator that's right yeah cuz a lot
of people don't know that's what I mean
like the refrigerators aren't that good
yet but once it's as easy as convenient
as a refrigerator leahy go cool yes you
tell me where to get a lot of lady Co
cools I'm interested
Georgia common yeah hit me up ya know
Tesla Tesla believes in the same thing
about how's that I do they just want to
build a better cheaper car right don't
waste money on it just keep talking
we're having no scope ease I gotta go
this girl text me back I'm excited I'd
text her back miss you wait a little bit
wait a little bit to CPU pixel to CPU
yeah the speed limit so just doing the
map she's not on the scope um she's on
the text wait three days wait three days
to text her back so I went through this
place okay you make a way bra no no no
no was she doing it nails that's the
thing else Joe
[Laughter]